bangalinet.com 2017-12-03

# Bengali Culture : Bengali Entertainment : Bengali Food : Privacy Statement

  | 

Log Files  
Like many other Web sites, Bangalinet makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable. What information do we collect?

We collect information from you when you subscribe to our newsletter or fill out a form. (like send ecard, mobile wallpaper, wallpaper, feedback form,  request form etc.

We do not collect your name and email address or any other information for just viewing our website.

What are cookies  
Sites use cookies to provide you with a more personalized and user-friendly experience. A cookie is a message that is sent to a browser from a Web server and stored on your computer's hard drive. Cookies help us keep track of the size of our audience, the frequency of visits to our Site and the areas that are most popular.We may have contracts with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.Do we use cookies?  
Bangalinet does not use cookies.  
However,Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookiesto serve ads on your site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit, to our sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy. DoubleClick DART Cookie  
.:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on www.bangalinet.com.  
.:: Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to www.bangalinet.com and other sites on the Internet.   
.:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL - http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html 

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include ....  
Google Adsense, Valueclick Media, Adbrite, Chitika, Amazon, Clicksor, Globe7, Guruji, infolink, shaadi etc.  
These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology in the advertisements and links that appear on Bangalinet and send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. We allow those third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit networkadvertising.org.

Bangalinet has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers. 

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. Bangalinet's privacy policy does not apply to and we cannot control the activities of such other advertisers or web sites. 

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

What do we use your information for?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: 

To improve our website  
(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)

To send periodic emails   
The email address you provide for newsletter,E-cards, Wallpapers and Tell a friend etc. may be used to send occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, or complete your request.

Bangalinet uses information received from you in the above categories of the site to process your requests and for no other reasons. The information gathered for sending ecard wallpaper web page etc. remains in our data base for a maximum period of 30 days and deleted thereafter.  
Subscription of newsletter: You can unsubscribe any time you want. Your information will be deleted automatically from our server and bangalinet will not send any company news, updates, related product or service information to your email.

Do we disclose any information to outside parties?   
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.Third party links

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

Online Privacy Policy Only

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

Your Consent

By using our site, you consent to our [privacy policy](http://www.freeprivacypolicy.com/).

Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below. 

This policy was last modified on 14th May 2012

Contacting Us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below. 

BANGALINET  
77/2D Ibrahimpur Road, Jadavpur  
Kolkata, West Bengal 700032  
INDIA  
info@bangalinet.com  
91-33-24139977
